export const quizData = [
  {
    question: 'AJAX',
    options: ['아작스', '에이작스', '아약스', '에이잭스'],
    wordDiacritic: 'ey-jaks',
    correctAnswer: '에이잭스',
  },
  {
    question: 'Private',
    options: ['프라이베이트', '프리베이트', '프라이빗', '프리빗'],
    wordDiacritic: 'prai-vit',
    correctAnswer: '프라이빗',
  },
  {
    question: 'Django',
    options: ['디장고', 'DJ앙고', '장고', '잔고'],
    wordDiacritic: 'jang-goh',
    correctAnswer: '장고',
  },
  {
    question: 'Azure',
    options: ['애저', '아저', '아주르', '아주어'],
    wordDiacritic: 'ey-zher',
    correctAnswer: '애저',
  },
  {
    question: 'Chore',
    options: ['쇼어', '쵸어', '코어', '촐'],
    wordDiacritic: 'chor',
    correctAnswer: '쵸어',
  },
  {
    question: 'width',
    options: ['위드스', '위스', '위드', '윗스'],
    wordDiacritic: 'with',
    correctAnswer: '윗스',
  },
  {
    question: 'height',
    options: ['헤이트', '헤잇', '하이트', '하잇'],
    wordDiacritic: 'hayt',
    correctAnswer: '하이트',
  },
  {
    question: 'async/await',
    options: [
      '어싱크/어웨잇',
      '싱크/웨잇',
      '에이싱크/어웨잇',
      '에이싱크/에이웨잇',
    ],
    wordDiacritic: 'a-sink/uh-weyt',
    correctAnswer: '에이싱크/어웨잇',
  },
  {
    question: 'relative',
    options: ['릴레이티브', '렐러티브', '레라티브', '렐라티브'],
    wordDiacritic: 'rel-uh-tiv',
    correctAnswer: '렐러티브',
  },
  {
    question: 'Nginx',
    options: ['느그엑스', '엔지닉스', '엔기닉스', '엔진엑스'],
    wordDiacritic: 'en-jin-eks',
    correctAnswer: '엔진엑스',
  },
];
